celebrating those tgifs yet not missing
on your weekend workout
acing your career goals
but prioritizing family time adapting to
new technology but switching off to
focus on your mental health you've
always been someone that strikes a
perfect balance to live life to the
fullest choosing a path of health and
peace of mind so to protect you even
better we at ICICI say Lombard and icic
Prudential life insurance have joined
forces presenting Eye shield a win-win
plan that offers dual benefits of health
and Life protection it comes with an
explosive restore benefit lets you claim
your medical expenses incurred
immediately after admission to the
hospital empowers you to get emergency
access to domestic air ambulance without
worrying about the expenses being
covered this plan gives you the
protection of a life cover up to the age
of 85. in case of an unfortunate demise
the nominee receives the life cover
amount therefore ensuring financial
support for the family in times of need
you can also choose to receive the life
cover amount as lump sum or monthly
income for 10 years or as a combination
of both eye Shields USB is its quick and
hassle-free claim service it secures
your loved ones with cashless
hospitalization and complimentary Health
checkups across our Network hospitals
and designated centers gets you tax
benefits under Section 80c and ATD of
income tax act 1961. now go ahead and
live your life to the fullest with a
win-win plan with convenience for more
details connect with our advisors today